A Guide to the Nelson C. Davis Papers FA048
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Printed Matter, 1895-1935; 3
  - Printed Matter - Monographs, 1901-1935; 3.3
    - Freitas, Lafayette de and Barnetto, Castro. "A lucta contra o Malaria." Rio de Janeiro, 1922. (Box 22, Folder 154)
    - Guter, B.A.R. and Rajamoney, P.D. "A Summary of Records on Anopheline Breeding Places in Malaya." Kualu Lumpar (Malaya), 1929. (Box 22, Folder 155)
    - Gordon, M.H. "Studies of the Viruses of Vaccinia and Variola." London, 1925. (Box 22, Folder 156)
    - Grassi, Battista. "Die Malaria." Jena, 1901. (Box 22, Folder 157)
    - Hacker, H.P. "How Oil Kills Anopheline Larvae." London, 1925. (Box 22, Folder 158)
    - Hill, Fred S. "Medical Certification for Marriage." New York, 1925. (Box 22, Folder 159)
    - Haslam, J.F.C. "Schistosomiasis and Malaria in Relation to Irrigation." London, 1929. (Box 22, Folder 160)
    - Hearle, Eric. "The Mosquitoes of the Lower Fraser Valley." Ottawa, 1926. (Box 22, Folder 161)
    - Hoehne, F.C. "Vegetates Antheliniticos." Sao Paulo, 1920. (Box 22, Folder 162)
    - Hoffman, Carlos. "La Distribucione Geografica de los Mosquitos Anopheles." Mexico, 1929. (Box 22, Folder 163)
    - Hoffman, Frederick L. "Malaria in Mississippi and Adjacent States." Newark, 1932. (Box 22, Folder 164)
    - Hoffman, Frederick L. "Malaria Problems." s.l., 1928. (Box 22, Folder 165)
    - Hoffman, Frederick L. "Present-Day trends in the Malaria Death Rate." Newark, 1931. (Box 22, Folder 166)
    - Holmes, Samuel J. "A Bibliography of Eugenics." Berkeley, 1924. (Box 22, Folder 167)
    - Hydrick, John Lee. "The Division of Public Health Education of the Public Health Service of the Netherlands East Indies." Weltevreden, c1927. (Box 22, Folder 168)
    - Ingram, Alexander and Meillon, Botha de. "A Mosquito Survey ... Part I." Johannesburg, 1927. (Box 22, Folder 169)
    - Ingram, Alexander and Meillon, Botha de. "A Mosquito Survey ... Part II." Johannesburg, 1927. (Box 22, Folder 170)
    - Instito de Butantan. "Collectanea de Trabalhos, 1901-1917." Sao Paulo, 1918. (Box 23, Folder 171)
    - Kemp, Emilio. "A Defenze da Sauda Publica no Rio Grande do Sol." Porto Alegre, 1916. (Box 23, Folder 172)
    - Kirkpatrick, T.W. "The Mosquitoes of Egypt." Cairo, 1925. (Box 23, Folder 173)
    - Klotz, OIkar. "Yellow Fever in West Africa." Baltimore, 1929. (Box 23, Folder 174)
    - Kraus, Rodolpho. "Instituto Soro therapico Butantan." Sao Paulo, 1923. (Box 23, Folder 175)
    - Kuczynski, Max H. "Der Erreger des Gelbfeibers." Berlin, 1929. (Box 23, Folder 176)
    - Lang, William. "A Handbook of British Mosquitoes." London, 1920. (Box 23, Folder 177)
    - Lang, William. "A Map Showing the Known Distribution in England and Wales of the Anopheline Mosquitoes." London, 1918. (Box 23, Folder 178)
    - Langlais, Marianne. "Prophylaxe du Paludisme au Maroc." Paris, 1929. (Box 23, Folder 179)
    - Lintz, Alcides and Parreiros, Decio. "Notes e Estudos Epidemiologico sobre a febre Amarella." Rio de Janeiro, 1930. (Box 23, Folder 180)
    - Lutz, Adolph. "Estudios de Zoologia y Parasitologia Venezolanas." Rio de Janeiro, 1928. (Box 23, Folder 181)
    - Maciel, Heraldo. "Contribuicao Paro o Estudo du Schisosomose Inestinal." Brasil, 1925. (Box 23, Folder 182)
    - Magalhaes, Gualberto Vicente de Paulo. "Contribuicao pessoal au Estudo da Bancroftose na Bahia." Bahia, 1928. (Box 23, Folder 183)
    - Marchose, E. "Fievre Juane." Paris, 1910. (Box 23, Folder 184)
    - Meillon, Botha de. "Illustrated Keys to the Full-Grown Larvae and Adults of South African Anopheline Mosquitoes." Johannesburg, 1931. (Box 23, Folder 185)
    - Martini, E. and Teubner, E. "Uber das Verhalten von Stechmucken besonders von 'Anopheles Maculipennis'." Leipzig, 1933. (Box 23, Folder 186)
    - "Memoria de la Campana contra el Paludismo." Madrid, 1925. (Box 23, Folder 187)
    - Mostardeiro Gertum, Jose Carlos. "Da syphilis e do seu tratamento pelo Silbersalvarsan." Porto Alegre, 1921. (Box 23, Folder 188)
    - Munoz Ochasa, Miguel. "Tratamento y Profilaxia de la Fiebre Amarilla en Guatamala." Porto Alegre, 1921. (Box 23, Folder 189)
    - Neuman, Sir George. "Recent Advances in Medical Education in England." London, 1923. (Box 23, Folder 190)
    - Nino, Flavio L. "Contribucion al Estudio de la Enferned de Chagas." Buenos Aires, 1929. (Box 23, Folder 191)
    - O'Connor, Francis W. "Researches in the Western Pacific." London, 1923. (Box 23, Folder 192)
    - Pachero, Octavio. "Relatoria: Municipia de Bom Muccesso." Muias Gereas, 1922. (Box 23, Folder 193)
    - Penna, Jose and Barbieri, Antonio. "El Paludismo." Buenos Aires, 1916. (Box 23, Folder 194)
    - Perroneito, Aldo. "Gli Studi di Camillo Galgi Sulla Malaria." Rome, 1929. (Box 23, Folder 195)
    - Petrocchi, Juana. "Mosquitos transmissores." Buenos Aires, 1924. (Box 23, Folder 196)
    - Petite, Auguste. "Virus Amaril." Paris, c1929. (Box 23, Folder 197)
    - Pinto, Cesar. "Simulidue da America Central e do Sul." Tucuman, 1931. (Box 23, Folder 198)
    - Puri, I.M. "Synoptic Tables for the Identification of the Fullgrown Larvae of the Indian Anopheline Mosquitoes." Calcutta, 1930. (Box 23, Folder 199)
    - "Report on the 'Anophelinae' of Mauritius." s.l., n.d. (Box 23, Folder 200)
    - Ribeiro da Fonseia, Olympio Oliveira. "Estudos solone os Flagellados Parasitos." Rio de Janeiro, 1915. (Box 23, Folder 201)
    - Ross, Sir Ronald, ed. "Observations on Malaria." London, 1919. (Box 23, Folder 202)
    - Russell, Paul L. "Malaria." Manila, 1931. (Box 23, Folder 203)
    - Sautet, E. "La Lutte contre de Paludisme en Corse." Paris, 1928. (Box 23, Folder 204)
    - Savas, C. and Cardamatis, J.P. "Ligue Antamalarienne hellenique." Athens, 1929. (Box 23, Folder 205)
    - Seljan, Shevo. "Viagens de Exploracao de Dais Yugo-Slavos." Ouro Preto (Brazil), 1919. (Box 23, Folder 206)
    - Senior-White, Ronald. "Catalogue of Indian Insects." Calcutta, 1923. (Box 23, Folder 207)
    - Sergeant, Edmund, ed. "La Decouverte de Laveran." Paris, 1929. (Box 23, Folder 208)
    - Sharp, David, ed. "Fauna Hawaiiensis." Cambridge, 1901. (Box 23, Folder 209)
    - Simonon, I.S. et al. "Experimental Studies of Dengue." Manila, 1921. (Box 23, Folder 210)
    - Soares do Nascimento, Alfredo. "Relatorio." Rio Grande (Brazil), 1922. (Box 23, Folder 211)
    - Soper, Fred L. "Rural and Jungle Yellow Fever." Bogota, 1935. (Box 23, Folder 212)
    - Strickland, C., et al. "A Report and Mosquito Survey of the Duars Tea Gardens." Calcutta, c.1926. (Box 24, Folder 213)
    - Strickland, C., et al. "Abridged Report on Malaria in the Assam Tea Gardens." Calcutta, c1926. (Box 24, Folder 214)
    - Swellengrebel, N.H. "De Anophelinen van Nederlandsch Oost-Indië." Amsterdam, 1921. (Box 24, Folder 215)
    - Thomson, John Gordon. "Researches on Blackwater Fever in Southern Rhodesia." London, 1924. (Box 24, Folder 216)
    - Torres, Octavio. "Hideyo Noguchi." Bahia, 1928. (Box 24, Folder 217)
    - Veintemillas, Felix. "Comprobacion de Fueos de la Peste en Bolivia." La Paz, 1933. (Box 24, Folder 218)
    - Veintemillas, Felix. "La Fiebre amarilla en Santa Cruz." La Paz, 1932. (Box 24, Folder 219)
    - Veintemillas, Felix. "Suplemento del Instituto Nacional de Bacteriologia." La Paz, 1933. (Box 24, Folder 220)
    - Wakemann, C. and Morrell, C.A. "The Blood and Urine in a Mild Case of Blackwater Fever." Lagos, 1929. (Box 24, Folder 221)
    - Wesenberg-Jung, C. "Contributino to the Biology of the Danish Culicidae." Copenhagen, 1920-1921. (Box 24, Folder 222)
    - Whitney, Jessamine S. "Facts and Figures about Tuberculosis." New York, 1931. (Box 24, Folder 223)
    - Wood, Thomas D., ed. "Health Education." New York, 1929. (Box 24, Folder 224)
    - Wright, Hamilton. "The Malarial Fevers of British Malaya." London, 1902. (Box 24, Folder 225)
  - Printed Matter - Periodicals, 1895-1935; 3.4
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by title.
    - Actas y Trabajos - Congreso Nacional de Medicina Argentina, 1926 (Box 24, Folder 226)
    - Analas del Departmento Nacional de Higiene (Argentina), 1911-1925 (Box 24, Folder 227)
    - Annales ... et de Medecine Coloniales, 1909 (Box 25, Folder 228)
    - Annales de L'Institute Pasteur, 1930 (Box 25, Folder 229)
    - Annals of Tropical Medicine and Parasitology, 1921-1933 (Box 25, Folder 230)
    - Annual Report of the Laboratory Services Division ... Uganda Malaria Survey Unit, 1930 (Box 25, Folder 231)
    - Archives de L'Institute Pasteur d'Algerie, 1928 (Box 25, Folder 232)
    - Archivos de Hygiene, 1929-1930 (Box 25, Folder 233)
    - Archivos do Museu Nacional do Rio de Janeiro, 1921 (Box 25, Folder 234)
    - Boletim Sanitario (Rio de Janeiro), 1922-1924 (Box 25, Folder 235)
    - Boletim Sanitario do Estado do Rio de Janeiro, 1924 (Box 25, Folder 236)
    - Boletin del Departmento de Unicinariasis, 1928-1931 (Box 25, Folder 237)
    - Boletin Official Departmental de Salubridad Mexico, 1928 (Box 25, Folder 238)
    - Boletin de la Oficina Sanitaria Panamericana, 1926-1927 (Box 25, Folder 239)
    - Boletin de la Union Panamericana, 1922 (Box 25, Folder 240)
    - Brasil-Medico, 1922-1933 (Box 25, Folder 241)
    - Bulletin (later, Review) of Applied Entomology, 1921-1934 (Box 26, Folder 242)
    - Bulletin-Mensuel, 1907 (Box 26, Folder 243)
    - Bulletin from the Institute for Medical Research Federated Malay States, 1924-1927 (Box 26, Folder 244)
    - Catecismos del Agricultor y del Ganadero: El Paludismo en el Campo, undated (Box 26, Folder 245)
    - Ceylon Government Documents, 1924-1925 (Box 26, Folder 246)
    - Collected Studies of the Department of Pathology and Bacteriology, University of Illinois, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 247)
    - Conference Africaine de la Fievre Juane, 1925 (Box 26, Folder 248)
    - Folia Biologica, 1931-1932 (Box 26, Folder 249)
    - Guide to the Insects of Connecticut, undated (Box 26, Folder 250)
    - Hooper Foundation Collected Reprints, 1916-1920 (Box 26, Folder 251)
    - Illinois Biological Monographs, 1911-1920 (Box 26, Folder 252)
    - Indian Journal of Medical Research (with Indian Medical Research Memoirs), 1916-1933 (Box 27, Folder 253)
    - Indice Bibliographico della Malaria, 1926-1928 (Box 27, Folder 254)
      See also Rivista di Malariologia.
    - Jamaica Public Health Bulletin, 1926-1929 (Box 27, Folder 255)
    - Japanese Journal of Experimental Medicine, 1930-1932 (Box 27, Folder 256)
    - Japanese Journal of Experimental Medicine, 1932-1935 (Box 28, Folder 257)
    - Johns Hopkins Hospital Reports, 1895 (Box 28, Folder 258)
    - La Semana Medica, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 259)
    - League of Nations - Health Organization Documents, 1924-1934 (Box 28, Folder 260)
    - Liverpool School of Tropical Medicine Memoirs, 1901-1902 (Box 28, Folder 261)
    - Mededeelingen von den Burgerlijken Geneesekungiden Deenst in Nederlandsch-Indie, 1919-1920 (Box 28, Folder 262)
    - Memorias do Instituto Butantan, 1930-1931 (Box 29, Folder 263)
    - Memorias do Instituto Oswaldo Cruz, 1909-1930 (Box 29, Folder 264)
    - (Le) Monde Medical, 1923 (Box 29, Folder 265)
    - National Medical Journal of China, 1931 (Box 29, Folder 266)
    - Paludism: Transactions of the Committee for the Study of Malaria in India, 1911 (Box 29, Folder 267)
    - Pernambro Vth Congresso Brasileiro de Hygiene, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 268)
    - Philippine Journal of Science, 1907 (Box 29, Folder 269)
    - Porto Rico Journal of Public Health, 1928-1930 (Box 30, Folder 270)
    - Proceedings of the Canal Zone Medical Association, 1910 (Box 30, Folder 271)
    - Proceedings of the Celebration of the 300th Anniversary of First Recognized Use of Cinchina, 1931 (Box 30, Folder 272)
    - Proceedings of the Annual New Jersey Mosquito Extermination Association, 1926-1929 (Box 30, Folder 273)
    - Proceedings of the Royal Society of Medicine, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 274)
    - Proceedings of the Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine, 1931-1933 (Box 30, Folder 275)
    - Publicacions de Mission de Estudios Patologia Regional (Argentina), 1932-1933 (Box 30, Folder 276)
    - Recommendations ... on the Lake Lowering Controversy ..., 1924 (Box 30, Folder 277)
    - Record of the Proceedings of the 1st International Malaria Congress, 1925 (Box 30, Folder 278)
      Also in French.
    - Report of the Commissioner of Health in Porto Rico, 1927 (Box 30, Folder 279)
    - Report of Dr. Israel Kligler Medical Research Unit, 1923 (Box 30, Folder 280)
    - Revista de Biologia e Hygiene, 1933 (Box 30, Folder 281)
    - Revista Brasileira de Ciurgia, 1934 (Box 30, Folder 282)
    - Revista Clinica e Pharmaceutica, 1935 (Box 30, Folder 283)
    - Revista de la Sociedad Entomologica Argentina, 1926 (Box 30, Folder 284)
    - Revista del Instituto Bacteriologicao (Argentina), 1920-1925 (Box 30, Folder 285)
    - Revue Generale de Medecine et de Chiurgia, 1930 (Box 30, Folder 286)
    - Revue Pratique des Laladies des Pays Chauds, 1922 (Box 30, Folder 287)
    - Rivista di Malariologica, 1927-1928 (Box 30, Folder 288)
      See also Indice Bibliographico della Malaria.
    - Salud y Sanidad, 1932-1933 (Box 30, Folder 289)
    - Scientific Reports from the Government Institute for Infectious Diseases, Tokyo Imperial University, 1922-1924 (Box 30, Folder 290)
    - Scientific Reports from the Government Institute for Infectious Diseases, Tokyo Imperial University, 1925-1927 (Box 31, Folder 291)
    - Seuola Superiore di Malariologica Lezioni, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 292)
    - Sociedad Argentina de Patologia Regional del Norte, 1926-1931 (Box 31, Folder 293)
    - Thompson Yates Laboratories Report, 1902 (Box 31, Folder 294)
    - Transactions of the Entomological Society of London, 1929 (Box 31, Folder 295)
    - Transactions of the Royal Society of Tropical Medicine and Hygiene, 1932-1933 (Box 31, Folder 296)
    - Transactions of the Royal Society of Tropical Medicine and Hygiene, 1933-1934 (Box 32, Folder 297)
    - Transactions of the Royal Society of Tropical Medicine and Hygiene - Sanitation Supplements, 1924-1925 (Box 32, Folder 298)
    - Tropical Diseases Bulletin, 1921-1934 (Box 32, Folder 299)
    - United Fruit Company Medical Department Annual Reports, 1924-1931 (Box 32, Folder 300)
    - United Fruit Company Medical Department Miscellaneous Documents, undated (Box 32, Folder 301)
    - Yellow Fever Bureau Bulletin - West Africa Reports and Supplements, 1915 (Box 32, Folder 302)